Exit Art "Reactions" exhibit collection
Prints & Photographs Division, Library of Congress
- Weinberg, Louise
  - Engine 7, 100 Duane Street, October 6, 2001, scala photo laser print; 2320; 988; Photograph of interior of fire house with the firemen's coats hung in a row
- Weiner
  - [Untitled], 2321; 236; "As the horizon metamorphizes..."
- Weinreich, Regina
  - [Untitled], 2322; 2161; Haiku
- Weinstein, Riva
  - An Art Prayer: 18 Life Affirming Objects from Nature, 2323; 1945; Vials and box
- Weinstein, Riva
  - An Art Prayer: 18 Life Affirming Objects from Nature, 2324; 1946; Small vial
- Weinstein, Riva
  - An Art Prayer: 18 Life Affirming Objects from Nature, 2325; 1947; Small box
- Weisberg, R.
  - [Untitled], 2326; 1205; WFMU Transpacific Sound Paradise
- Weiss, Irving
  - [Untitled], 2327; 66; Artwork via mail
- Weiss, Irving
  - Tower, photograph; 2328; 2089; Photo of tower of writing
- Weiss, Jessica
  - [Untitled], 2329; 1489; Flower in center
- Wells, Lee A.
  - The Wonderwoman, mixed media; 2330; 1376; Image of fragmented wonderwoman
- Wenker, Marilyn
  - Makeshift Gas Masks Washington Square Park September 12, ink jet print; 2331; 1578; 3 girls in WSP
- Wennermark, Erik
  - [Untitled], watercolor/drawing; 2332; 154; Watercolor/drawing of man
- West, Richard
  - [Untitled], 2333; 243
- Whalen, Marc
  - My name is Marc and my friend Joey worked on the 105th floor of No. 1 World Trade Center..., picture (digital print); 2334; 670
- Wheeler, Brian
  - [Untitled], drawing with text; 2335; 972
- Wheeler, Jeff
  - [Untitled], 2336; 971
- Wheeler, Patricia
  - [Untitled], 2337; 78; Artwork via mail
- White, Lili
  - Reaction, collage; 2338; 542
- Waite, Mary
  - [Untitled], drawing and text; 2339; 1145
- White, S.
  - [Untitled], 2340; 864
- White, Susan
  - [Untitled], 2341; 173; 1 of 2 photos
- White, Susan
  - [Untitled], 2342; 180; 2 of 2 photos
- Wigdor, Keith
  - Another NSA Meeting, 2343; 169
- Wilkins, Jason
  - [Untitled], 2344; 1918; Fireman
- Wilkinson, Ellen
  - [Untitled], cut out black on white; 2345; 657
- Wilkinson, Jeanne
  - Peace in 2002, 2346; 604; Triangles and sunburst
- Wilkinson, Laura
  - [Untitled], color print of photo; 2346b; 3268
- William, Dale
  - Our September, mixed media w/collage on canvas; 2347; 708
- Williams, Genevieve
  - [Untitled], 2349; 1189; Crouching figure
- Williams, Patrick
  - [Untitled], 2350; 984; Image of an abstract square face with glasses
- Williams, Ronnie Christopher
  - We've Got to Pray, 2351; 1885; Poem
- Williams, Ronnie Christopher
  - [Untitled], digital image; 2352; 1886; Close up of head
- Williams, Ronnie Christopher
  - [Untitled], digital image; 2353; 1887; Cher doll
- Williams, Ronnie Christopher
  - [Untitled], digital image; 2354; 1888; Barbara doll
- Williams, Ronnie Christopher
  - [Untitled], digital image; 2355; 1889; Barbara doll w/mirror
- Williams, Ronnie Christopher
  - [Untitled], digital image; 2356; 1890; Barbara doll in forest
- Williams, Rosemary
  - [Untitled], 2357; 1198; Lots of squares
- Wilson, Laura Sharp
  - Oiled Spoiled, 2358; 905; 1 of 2
- Wilson, Laura Sharp
  - Detainees, 2359; 904; 2 of 2
- Wilson, Marion
  - [Untitled], digital image; 2360; 990; Abstract image (2 of 2)
- Wilson, Marion
  - [Untitled], digital image; 2361; 989; Abstract image (1 of 2)
- Wilson, Michael
  - [Untitled], photograph; 2362; 1416; Photo of John Ashcroft with the words "I will guide thee with mine eyes - Psalm 32"
- Winard, Rosalie
  - [Untitled], photo; 2363; 346; The end of the world as we knew it
- Winborn, Rachel
  - [Untitled], 2364; 1696; Face in mask
- Winckelman, Hanna J.
  - [Untitled], 2365; 212; Part of group from students of the Hudson School, "Dreams"
- Winsor, Jodie
  - [Untitled], 2366; 1149; United We Stand
- Winters, Peggy Joan
  - [Untitled], 2367; 104; Artwork via mail
- Wise, W. Randy
  - [Untitled], 2368; 906; O beautiful
- Wixon, Nathaniel
  - [Untitled], 2369; 29; Poem via email
- Wojcik, Vicki King
  - Union Square, 2370; 399
- Wolanczyk, Rozanne
  - [Untitled], 2371; 192
- Wolfe, Sara
  - [Untitled], paint on paper; 2372; 2049; Abstract design resembling smoke
- Wolff, Karen Frimkess
  - My Tolerant Western Heart, 2373; 1051; Tora
- Wolin, David E.
  - [Untitled], acrylic on paper; 2374; 899; Slash marks
- Wong, Paul
  - Don’t Believe in Santa, 2375; 3039
- Wong, Paul
  - [Untitled], 2376; 3052; 4 pictures of Asian man with beard
- Wolowski, Eddie
  - [Untitled], 2377; 1355
- Wong, Rita
  - [Untitled], 2378; 3031; Poem via email
- Wood, A. Robin
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 2379; 1496; Abstract images and handwritten text
- Woodruff, Suzan
  - Psyche & Eros, 2380; 1576; Butterfly
- Woodward, Karen Z.
  - [Untitled], color copy; 2380b; 3261
- Wooster, Ann
  - [Untitled], text on paper; 2381; 1523; Sheet of paper, first sentence: "We came back and everything was usual until September 11 changed the whole nature of 2001"
- Wright, Robert
  - [Untitled], 2382; 444
- Wright, Sara
  - The Voice of the Forest, 2383; 1338; Letter and poem
- Wyllie, Nancy E.
  - Taliban Trinity, digital image; 2384; 921; Crying women
- Wyndham, Tamara
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 2385; 1369
- Xing Lei, Pan
  - [Untitled], 2386
- Yang, Hee Sung
  - [Untitled], 2387; 574; Bubbles
- Yankowitz, Nina
  - [Untitled], 2388; 1188; Horizontal bands
- Yankus, Marc
  - After the screaming I ran to the roof with my camera and started shooting. I felt nothing. It was like watching a movie..., photograph (digital print); 2389; 1924; 1924-1928; "after the screaming..."
- Yankus, Marc
  - [Untitled], 2390; 1925; 1924-1928; two men watching towers
- Yankus, Marc
  - [Untitled], 2391; 1926; 1924-1928; WTC smoking
- Yankus, Marc
  - [Untitled], 2392; 1927; 1924-1928; church and WTC smoking
- Yankus, Marc
  - [Untitled], 2393; 1928; 1924-1928; church and WTC smoking (horizontal)
- Yaron, Dror
  - [Untitled], 2394; 1179; Big American flag
- Yarrington, Jo
  - [Untitled], 2395; 682; Diptych, two cruciform images 1 of 2
- Yarrington, Jo
  - [Untitled], 2396; 681; Diptych, two cruciform images 2 of 2
- Yasumaru, Junko
  - [Untitled], 2397; 725
- Yeadon, Bill
  - A World Peace Meditation, 2398; 969
- Yerman, Marcia G.
  - [Untitled], 2399; 1327; Text and drawing of figure
- Yim, Mie
  - [Untitled], 2400; 1778; Girl w/bullets.
- Yonda, Andrew
  - [Untitled], 2401; 1208; Window with writing
- York, Nora
  - [Untitled], digital image; 2402; 1407; Faded text on abstract background
- Yoshida, Yoko
  - Sorrows or Tears, 2403; 2193; Stamps
- Young, Daniel
  - Curb your god, print (digital print); 2404; 54; Mailed
- Young, Penn
  - [Untitled], 2405; 412; Smudge/brushstroke
- Youngs, Ted
  - [Untitled], 2406; 18; Text via email
- Yu, Zhang
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 2407; 1810; NYC skyline
- Yu, Zhang
  - [Untitled], digital photograph; 2408; 1811
- Yu, Zhang
  - [Untitled], digital photograph; 2409; 1812; Crab w/NY
- Yung, Susan L.
  - # 3 - 4 PM 9/11/Sex, photograph; 2410; 2051; Photo of woman in bikini w/smoking WTC in background
- Yung, Susan L.
  - The Collapse, photograph; 2411; 2052; Shot of burning WTC
- Yung, Susan L.
  - B4 Collapse, photograph; 2412; 2053; Shot of burning WTC
- Zack, Connie
  - The View from 14th Street, photo collage; 2413; 608
- Zalk, Jason
  - [Untitled], 2414; 411; Scribbly
- Zambrano, Vincent
  - [Untitled], watercolor; 2415; 878; Watercolor of firefighter
- Zanni, Carlo
  - [Untitled], internet print; 2415b; 2277; Re: actions
- Zarate, Alicia
  - [Untitled], 2416; 2291; Emailed
- Zardo, Marcio
  - Mundo Mudo, 2417; 3085
- Zaso, John
  - [Untitled], 2418; 2029; Famous fries
- Zaso, John
  - [Untitled], 2419; 2028; McDonald's world
- Zedd, Nick
  - [Untitled], 2420; 216; "The past and the future..."
- Zellen, Jody
  - The Life & Death of Buildings, 2421; 90; 1 of 3 artworks by mail
- Zellen, Jody
  - The Life & Death of Buildings, 2422; 91; 2 of 3 artworks by mail
- Zellen, Jody
  - The Life & Death of Buildings, 2423; 92; 3 of 3 artworks by mail
- Zeller, Dan
  - Downtown Arteries, 2424; 1181; Downtown manh.
- Zercher, D. Lowell
  - [Untitled], crayon on paper; 2425; 806; Crayon drawing of a spiral with stars around it
- Zerpa, Carlos
  - [Untitled], color copy; 2425b; 3245
- Zet, Adam
  - [Untitled], 2426; 2035; No and stick figure
- Zet, Martin
  - [Untitled], 2427; 3019; Everybody, text via email
- Zhang, Lansheng
  - [Untitled], digital image; 2429; 1952; Falling WTC
- Ziehofer, William
  - [Untitled], laser print of a collage; 2430; 752; A candle in lower right hand corner
- Zilenziger, Rebecca
  - A Visual Response to Sept. 11, 2001, photograph; 2431; 1499; Photo of an empty room with a dress hanging from ceiling and the TV on
- Zimmerman, Natalie
  - Throwing Weight, still image of a video performance; 2432; 1362; Photo of the artist lying on her back pushing backwards
- Zinnes, Alice
  - [Untitled], digital images of oil on canvas; 2433; 817; Two paintings, one done before 9/11 and one done after 9/11
- Zinnes, Harriet
  - Bombing Has Started, 2434; 38
- Zinnes, Harriet
  - Men, Helmets, Guns, 2434b; 3324
- Zonus, A.
  - In Memory of 9/11/01, painting; 2436; 920
- Zweibel, Jane E.
  - [Untitled], 2437; 1765; Subway car
- Zweifel, Thomas D.
  - Xmas card NY skyline, comp. print out; 2438; 3242
- Hall, Tom
  - [Untitled], ink on paper; 2440; 3327; Drawing of two bright yellow towers w/black ink and marker on white paper
- Morales, Rafael
  - [Untitled], ink on paper; 2448; 3328; Drawing of Twin Towers Site (1 of 2)
- Morales, Rafael
  - [Untitled], ink on paper; 2449; 3329; Drawing of Twin Towers Site (2 of 2)
- Borgman, Kurt
  - [Untitled], digital image; 2450; 3330; Image of worn American flag with Afghan soldiers in lower right corner
- Stavrolakes, Rena Georgette
  - St Nicholas Greek Orthodox Church: In Memoriam, text on paper; 2451; 3331; 9 paragraph essay on two pages
- Morrison, James
  - Remembrance Cards (World Trade Center), installation of envelopes with contents created by the public; 2452; 3332
- Van Leeuwen, Gerda
  - [Untitled], text w/digital image; 2453; 3333; Penis towers
- Congdon, Roark
  - [Untitled], text, plastic flag, and scrap; 2454; 3334
- Burach, Todd
  - A Mile From Normal, poem; 2455; 3335; Essays/poems from H.S. students, Ocean Grove, NJ
- Santoro, Michael
  - Hall of Hopes, poem; 2456; 3336; Essays/poems from H.S. students, Ocean Grove, NJ
- Fogel, Doreen
  - [Untitled], poem; 2457; 3337; Essays/poems from H.S. students, Ocean Grove, NJ
- Caruana, Chelsea
  - [Untitled], poem; 2458; 3338; Essays/poems from H.S. students, Ocean Grove, NJ
- Manalpan High School
  - [Untitled], poem; 2459; 3339; Essays/poems from H.S. students, Ocean Grove, NJ
- Costello, Drew
  - [Untitled], poem; 2460; 3340; Essays/poems from H.S. students, Ocean Grove, NJ
- Flammia, Dino
  - Make It Stop, poem; 2461; 3341; Essays/poems from H.S. students, Ocean Grove, NJ
- Efron, Jill
  - [Untitled], poem; 2462; 3342; Essays/poems from H.S. students, Ocean Grove, NJ
- Cohen, Jacqueline
  - The Day Called 911, poem; 2463; 3343; Essays/poems from H.S. students, Ocean Grove, NJ
- Sloat, Richard
  - [Untitled], 2464; 3344; NYC Free - red and blue writing with black figures in circle
- Howland, Becky
  - Cedar Street/The Thing, charcoal drawing; 2465; 3345; The Thing - poem and drawing of ground zero
- Howland, Becky
  - [Untitled], drawing; 2466; 3346; The sun with "There will never be a war fought over solar energy..."
- Tsiklauri, Gulnara
  - [Untitled], 2467; 3347; Hands
- Unknown
  - [Untitled], digital print; 2468; 3348; Via email, patels, shapes
- Barros, Rita
  - [Untitled], 2469; 3349; Camels and buildings w/smoke "smoke, stench..."
- Pinto, Anna
  - [Untitled], 2470; 3350; Calligraphic reaction; skinny cardboard with poetry from Joyce and Whitman
- Shandler, Manju
  - Gesture, digital print; 2471; 3351; Fireman from behind
- Moran, Barbara Baillet
  - Filling Spaces, poem; 2472; 3352; Can ashes fill a space
- Hiuni, Dahn
  - September 11 Monuments, 2473; 3353; Flyer for class
- [Anonymous]
  - [Untitled], digital print; 2474; 3354; Pink with gas mask-looking figures or aliens?
- Hendricks, Geoffrey
  - [Untitled], 2475; 3355; I Ching at WTC
- Bougopoulos, Melody
  - [Untitled], 2476; 3356; Purge evil
- Bougopoulos, Melody
  - [Untitled], 2477; 3357; Solidarity
- Bougopoulos, Melody
  - [Untitled], 2478; 3358; Freedom, justice, peace
- Bougopoulos, Melody
  - [Untitled], 2479; 3359; Protect each other
- Payne, Elizabeth
  - WTC, 1978-2001, collage; 2480; 3360; Two pics of WTC
- Mackinnon, Don
  - 9/11 Terrorist Disaster, charcoal and oil paint; 2481; 3361; Burning WTC
- Baerg, Jason
  - NEW YORK CITY, text on paper; 2482; 3362; NEW YORK CITY!... Times... TIME... Creatively the city has been beating the pulse of my existence for a LONG
- Salley, Rael
  - [Untitled], text on paper; 2483; 3363; Until the philosophy, which holds one race superior and another
- Jones, Vanessa
  - Married to a Muslim Truck Driver, text on paper; 2484; 3364; It may sometimes be wondered how Anglo Saxon (read English speaking and white - currently Australian) women are married to Arabic men of Egyptian...
- Yaw, Troy Edison
  - The Truth, text on paper; 2485; 3365; We have to do what is right We cannot fall without giving up a fight; Terrorism is not part of my dream
- Roth, Moria
  - The Mute Room, Library of Maps # 19, text on paper; 2486; 3366; Slowly the librarians pieced together the stories of the Blind Child and the Mute Singer
- Ziehofer, William
  - Candle of Hope, laser print of photo collage; 2487; 3376; Dark brown background with handwritten black text and oval black and white photo in foreground
- Kennedy, Stephen
  - The Tri-Towers, pencil on paper; 2490; 3367; Series of designs for a three tower complex (1 of 4)
- Kennedy, Stephen
  - The Tri-Towers, pencil on paper; 2491; 3368; Series of designs for a three tower complex (2 of 4)
- Kennedy, Stephen
  - The Tri-Towers, pencil on paper; 2492; 3369; Series of designs for a three tower complex (2 of 4)
- Kennedy, Stephen
  - The Tri-Towers, pencil on paper; 2493; 3370; Series of designs for a three tower complex (2 of 4)
- Lin, Jonathan
  - [Untitled], digital image; 2494; 3371; Is this your definition of PEACE?
- Tommerup, Mette
  - [Untitled], ink on paper; 2495; 3372
- Chambers, Robert
  - [Untitled], ink on paper; 2496; 3373; Curvy black lines on white paper
- Andrea, Gordon
  - Veiliance, performed documentation; 2497; 3374; A series of digital images documenting the performance
- Brady, Mary Jo
  - The Response, text on paper; 2498; 3375; 6 stanza poem on white paper
- Goldberg, Marcy
  - Terrorism Suck, digital image; 2499; 3377; Square montage of images of red lifesavers and Osama Bin Laden with the words "Terrorism Suck" (1 of 4)
- Goldberg, Marcy
  - Terrorism Suck, digital image; 2500; 3378; Light green background with black and white collaged twin towers in foreground (2 of 4)
- Goldberg, Marcy
  - Terrorism Suck, digital image; 2501; 3379; Solid purple background with image of two silver life saver rolls in foreground. The roll on the right is partilly opened (3 of 4)
- Goldberg, Marcy
  - Terrorism Suck, digital image; 2502; 3380; Black and white digital collage of the word, "missing" (4 of 4)
- Malone, Kelly Ann
  - Distant Witness, text on paper; 2503; 3381; I don't live close; I did not hear the thunder crash...
- Doyle, Richard T.
  - Fourth of July, text on paper; 2504; 3382; Outside my bedroom window as far as my young eyes could see...
- Dorn, Fairfax
  - [Untitled], 2505; 3383; People looking up
- Teriananda
  - [Untitled], 2506; 3384; Poem with a green pencil drawing mounted on a piece of paper bag "New York is not a theme park..."